{
  "response_code": 0,
  "results": [
    {
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "category": "General Knowledge",
      "question": "What organ of the body produces bile?",
      "correct_answer": "Liver",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Gallbladder",
        "Pancreas",
        "Stomach"
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "category": "General Knowledge",
      "question": "What element has the chemical symbol Kr?",
      "correct_answer": "Krypton",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Kerosine",
        "Kineticium",
        "Curium"
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "category": "General Knowledge",
      "question": "In DC comics where does the Green Arrow (Oliver Queen) live?",
      "correct_answer": "Star City",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Central City",
        "Gotham City",
        "Metropolis"
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "category": "General Knowledge",
      "question": "In which fast food chain can you order a Jamocha Shake?",
      "correct_answer": "Arby&#039;s",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "McDonald&#039;s",
        "Burger King",
        "Wendy&#039;s"
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "category": "General Knowledge",
      "question": "A criminal who has &ldquo;cooked the books&rdquo; has engaged in what kind of illegal behavior?",
      "correct_answer": "Accounting Fraud",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Money Laundering",
        "Extortion",
        "Blackmail"
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "category": "General Knowledge",
      "question": "What is on display in the Madame Tussaud&#039;s museum in London?",
      "correct_answer": "Wax sculptures",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Designer clothing",
        "Unreleased film reels",
        "Vintage cars"
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "category": "General Knowledge",
      "question": "What style of beer will typically have a higher than average hop content?",
      "correct_answer": "India Pale Ale",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Stout",
        "Extra Special Bitter",
        "Scotch Ale"
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "category": "General Knowledge",
      "question": "What is the closest planet to our solar system&#039;s sun?",
      "correct_answer": "Mercury",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Mars",
        "Jupiter",
        "Earth"
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "category": "General Knowledge",
      "question": "Which one of these is not a typical European sword design?",
      "correct_answer": "Scimitar",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Falchion",
        "Ulfberht",
        "Flamberge"
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "category": "General Knowledge",
      "question": "What is the famous Papa John&#039;s last name?",
      "correct_answer": "Schnatter",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Chowder",
        "Williams",
        "ANDERSON"
      ]
    }
  ]
}